Guide to the Chih H. Wang Papers 1947-1984
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections & Archives Research Center
Chih H. Wang Papers
1947-1984
1960-1980
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections & Archives Research Center Special Collections & University Archives Research Center 121 The Valley Library Oregon State University Corvallis, OR 97331-4501 Phone: 541-737-2075 Email: scarc@oregonstate.edu Web: http://scarc.library.oregonstate.edu
MSS Wang
Wang, Chih Hsing, 1917-
13.8 cubic feet, including 24 film transparencies 42 boxes
The Chih H. Wang Papers are composed of materials created and assembled by Wang as a faculty member of the Oregon State University Chemistry Department, Director of the OSU Radiation Center, and Head of the Institute of Nuclear Science and Engineering. Materials include professional correspondence, OSU Chemistry Department and Radiation Center research records, workshop, conference, and training program files, OSU administrative records, publications by Wang, and subject files related to chemistry, nuclear science, and nuclear power policy and legislation. The Wang Papers document Wang's career, the founding and development of the OSU Radiation Center, and the growth of nuclear science research and training during the 1960s and 1970s.
Biographical Note:
Chih H. Wang was Professor of Chemistry, Director of the Radiation Center, and Head of the Institute of Nuclear Science and Engineering at Oregon State University. He was responsible for the growth of nuclear science research on the Oregon State University campus and the creation of the OSU Radiation Center.
Wang was born in 1917 in Shanghai, China. He attended the National University of Shandong where he earned his B.S. in chemistry. Wang's studies and employment were disrupted by the Second Sino-Japanese War and later World War II but, beginning in 1938, Wang found work as a chemistry instructor at West China Union University. In 1945, Wang immigrated to the United States where he enrolled at Oregon State College. There, he earned his Ph.D. in organic chemistry. In 1950, Wang joined the OSU Chemistry Department as an instructor, where he focused on research in biochemistry, plant physiology, microbiology, and radiation biology. As a result of his aggressive research agenda, Wang earned his full professorship. Wang's use of radioisotopes in research resulted in a push for improved radiation research facilities on the OSU campus. In 1958, Wang drafted the first of three proposals requesting funds to build a radiation center at OSU. Funding was granted in 1960 and construction of the facility began in 1962. The TRIGA reactor (OSTR) was installed and activated in the OSU Radiation Center in 1967. Wang was named Director of the Radiation Center and Head of the Institute of Nuclear Science and Engineering--a position he filled until his retirement in 1984.
The Chih H. Wang Papers consist of materials generated and assembled by Wang, a faculty member of the OSU Chemistry Department, Head of the OSU Institute of Nuclear Science and Engineering, and Director of the OSU Radiation Center, between 1947 and 1984. The collection includes professional correspondence with researchers, corporate partners, colleagues in Taiwan, and OSU administrators. The collection also includes records of research conducted by the OSU Chemistry Department and at the OSU Radiation Center in cooperation with the Atomic Energy Commission, the National Science Foundation, the U.S. Navy, Exxon, DARPA (Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency), the U.S. Air Force, and others; correspondence and administrative files from workshops, conferences, and training programs including the Academic Year Institute in Nuclear Science and a multi-year training program for employees of the Taiwan Power Company (TaiPower); and records of the founding, growth, and operation of the OSU Radiation Center.
The collection also includes abstracts and offprints of publications by Wang in the fields of chemistry, biochemistry, and radiation sciences and includes research into the biochemistry of microorganisms, the effects of inorganic compounds of biological systems, the development of nuclear power, and nuclear technology instruction. Many of these publications were co-authored with other Oregon State University faculty, including Bert E. Christensen, Vernon H. Cheldelin, Donald J. Reed, and Frank N. Dost. Additionally, the collection contains subject files assembled by Wang relating to chemistry and biochemistry, radiation sciences, and nuclear power policy and legislation.
The Chih H. Wang Papers are arranged into six series: I: Correspondence, 1964-1984; II: Research Project Records, 1952-1983; III: Training and Education Project Records, 1958-1981; IV: OSU Radiation Center Administrative Records, 1950-1984; V: Publications, 1947-1972; VI: Subject Files, 1949-1980.
The collection is open for research.
The Chih H. Wang Papers were accessioned from the OSU Radiation Center in July 2013.
Related Materials
An oral history conducted with Chih Wang is located in the Horner Museum Oral History Collection (OH 10). Other materials pertaining to chemistry and nuclear science research and instruction at Oregon State University include the Radiation Center Records (RG 202), John C. Ringle Papers (MSS Ringle), E. Dale Trout Papers (MSS Trout), "How OSU Grew Nuclear Science" Oral Histories (OH 16). Chemistry Department Records (RG 098), Science Research Institute Records (RG 014), and the College of Science Records (RG 024). Additional materials relating to nuclear science and engineering include the Barton C. Hacker Papers (MSS HackerB), Barton C. and Sally L. Hacker Nuclear Affairs Collection (MSS Hacker), Leonard M. Maki Nuclear Power Collection (MSS Maki), Charter Heslep Papers (MSS Heslep), Ava Helen and Linus Pauling Papers (MSS Pauling), and the History of Atomic Energy Collection (RB Energy).
Cheldelin, Vernon H.; Christensen, Bert Einar, 1904-; Dost, Frank N.; Reed, D. J.
Oregon State University. Institute of Nuclear Science and Engineering.; Oregon State University. Radiation Center.; Taiwan dian li gong si.; National Science Foundation (U.S.); U.S. Atomic Energy Commission.
Chemistry--Research--Oregon.; Chemistry--Study and teaching (Higher)--Oregon.; Microbiology--Research--Oregon.; Nuclear energy--Environmental aspects--United States.; Nuclear energy--Law and legislation--United States.; Nuclear engineering--Oregon.; Nuclear engineering--Study and teaching--Oregon--Corvallis.; Nuclear physics--Research--Oregon.; Nuclear reactors--Oregon--Corvallis.
Film transparencies.
Colleges and Universities; Energy Production; Science; Technology; Corvallis; Photographs
- Correspondence, 1964-1984; Series I
  Series I is composed of correspondence between Chih Wang and colleagues, researchers, OSU administrators, trainees, politicians, and other individuals associated with the field of nuclear engineering. The majority of materials in this series relates to Wang's duties as director of the OSU Radiation Center and includes correspondence regarding research conducted at the Radiation Center, training and education in the nuclear sciences, scientific equipment and instrumentation, funding for Radiation Center activities, and intra-university administrative procedures. The series includes correspondence regarding participation in professional organizations such as Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc.; collaboration with corporate partners including the Eugene Water & Electric board and the Jersey Nuclear Company in site studies, nuclear power research and policy efforts, and training and conference activities; and the purchase of goods and services provided by Atomic Industries, Wah Chang, and other organizations. This series also contains a group of English and Chinese-language materials concerning Chih H. Wang's professional relationship with individuals involved in nuclear science and engineering research in Taiwan including members of the Taiwan Power Company (TaiPower), National Taiwan University, and the Chinese government in Taiwan.
  - Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 1.1)
  - Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box-folder 1.2)
  - Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., 1976-1984 (Box-folder 1.3)
  - Atomics International, 1972 (Box-folder 1.4)
  - Ebasco Services, Inc., 1975-1978 (Box-folder 1.5)
  - Eugene Water & Electric Board, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 1.6)
  - General Electric Co., 1967-1980 (Box-folder 1.7)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 1.8)
  - Hewlett Packard, 1981 (Box-folder 2.1)
  - Jersey Nuclear Company, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 2.2)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1964-1975 (Box-folder 2.3)
  - National Institutes of Health, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 2.4)
  - National Research Council, 1965-1984 (Box-folder 2.5)
  - Oregon State Board of Higher Education, 1972-1984 (Box-folder 2.6)
  - OSU Agricultural Experiment Station, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 2.7)
  - OSU Air Resource Center, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2.8)
  - OSU Archives, 1967 (Box-folder 2.9)
  - OSU Business Affairs Office, 1966-1983 (Box-folder 2.10)
  - OSU Dean of Faculty, 1969-1983 (Box-folder 2.11)
  - OSU Department of Agricultural Chemistry, 1973 (Box-folder 2.12)
  - OSU Department of Atmospheric Sciences, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 2.13)
  - OSU Department of Biochemistry & Biophysics, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 2.14)
  - OSU Department of Chemistry, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 3.1)
  - OSU Department of General Science, 1967-1984 (Box-folder 3.2)
  - OSU Environmental Health Sciences Center, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 3.3)
  - OSU Extension Service, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 3.4)
  - OSU Laboratory Animal Resources, 1969-1981 (Box-folder 3.5)
  - OSU Nuclear Science and Engineering Institute, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 3.6)
  - OSU Planning and Institutional Research, 1968-1982 (Box-folder 3.7)
  - OSU President's Office, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 3.8)
  - OSU Radiation Center, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 3.9)
  - OSU Radiation Center, 1967-1981 (Box-folder 4.1)
  - OSU Radiation Center, 1972 (Box-folder 4.2)
  - OSU Research Office, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 4.3)
  - OSU Vice President for Administration, 1966-1984 (Box-folder 4.4)
  - Pacific Power & Light Company, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4.5)
  - Portland General Electric Company, 1968-1981 (Box-folder 4.6)
  - U.S. Energy Research & Development Administration, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4.7)
  - U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) Corvallis Environmental Research Laboratory, 1968-1982 (Box-folder 4.8)
  - U.S. Federal Energy Administration, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 5.1)
  - Wah Chang Corporation, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 5.2)
  - Victor G. Atiyeh, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 5.3)
  - Les Aucoin, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 5.4)
  - Lamar P. Bupp, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 5.5)
  - William L. Lappenbusch, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 5.6)
  - Bob Packwood, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 5.7)
  - Milosh Popovich, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 5.8)
  - Robert Straub, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 5.9)
  - Thomas Sugihara, 1981 (Box-folder 5.10)
  - Mae Yih, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 5.11)
  - General Administrative Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 5.12)
  - General Administrative Correspondence, 1970-1984 (Box-folder 5.13)
  - National Taiwan University Chemistry Research Center, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 5.14)
  - Kawei Chen, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 5.15)
  - Shang-Shiang Hsu, 1976 (Box-folder 5.16)
  - Huey-Jo Kuo, 1980 (Box-folder 6.1)
  - Chio-Min Yang, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 6.2)
  - General Taiwanese Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 6.3)
  - General Taiwanese Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 6.4)
  - General Taiwanese Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 6.5)
  - General Taiwanese Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 6.6)
- Research Project Records, 1952-1983; Series II
  Series II is comprised of proposals, contracts, reports, research materials, budgetary documents, and correspondence relating to research projects conducted by the OSU Department of Chemistry and, later, the OSU Radiation Center on behalf of the Defense Advanced Research Programs Agency (DARPA), Exxon, the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), the National Science Foundation (NSF), the U.S. Air Force, the U.S. Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), the U.S. Navy, and other organizations. Topics addressed in the series include recovery of uranium from seawater, studies of missile pollution, and application of radiotracers. Also included in this series are materials related to grant funding for technical improvements to the OSU Radiation Center.
  - DARPA Contract: "Biochemical and Pharmacological Studies of l, l-Dimethylhydrazine," DA18-108-CML-7154, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 6.7)
  - Exxon Nuclear Company Contract: "Low-Grade Uranium Resources--Seawater Project," 78-232-L, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 6.8)
  - Exxon Nuclear Company Contract: "Low-Grade Uranium Resources--Seawater Project," 78-232-L, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6.9)
  - Exxon Nuclear Company Contract: "Low-Grade Uranium Resources--Seawater Project," 78-232-L, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 7.1)
  - Exxon Nuclear Company Contract: "Low-Grade Uranium Resources--Seawater Project," 78-232-L, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 7.2)
  - NASA Grant: "Apollo Sample Return Program", 1966-1968 (Box-folder 7.3)
  - NASA Grant: "On the Study of Elemental Abundances in Meteoritic and Terrestrial Matter," NGR-38-002-020, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 7.4)
  - NASA Grant: "Neutron Activation Analysis of Extraterrestrial Particles and Hypervelocity Retained in Impacted Craters," NGL-38-002-032, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 7.5)
  - NSF Grant: "Instrumentation for Carbohydrate Catabolism," G-21271, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 7.6)
  - NSF Grant: "Neutron Activation Equipment," GK-1046, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 7.7)
  - NSF Grant: "Neutron Diffraction Equipment to Accommodate Materials Engineering Research Programs" GK-1660, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 7.8)
  - NSF Grant: "Light Element Miscibilities in Glass," GK-2043, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 7.9)
  - NSF Grant: "Neutron Generator Equipment to Accommodate Research Programs in Materials Engineering and Science," GK-3808, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 7.10)
  - NSF Grant: "Reactor Heat-Exchanger Equipment to Accommodate Material Engineering at the OSU Radiation Center," GK-24639, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7.11)
  - NSF Proposal: "Financial Support of the Research Reactor Facility", 1962-1964 (Box-folder 8.1)
  - NSF Proposal: "The Wind Energy Resources of a Large River Valley System", 1974 (Box-folder 8.2)
  - NSF Proposal: "Vertical Differentiation in Engineering and Supportive Technical Occupations," Sally Hacker, 1980 (Box-folder 8.3)
  - NSF Proposal Reviews, 1980 (Box-folder 8.4)
  - OSU Department of Animal Science: "Determination of Bioavailability of Selenium", 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8.5)
  - OSU Environmental Health Science Center: "A Study of Pollutant Flow in the Willamette River and its Tributaries Using the Rare-Earth Spiking Method", 1968-1970 (Box-folder 8.6)
  - OSU Nutrition Research Institute: "Trace Elements in Human Blood Samples", 1967-1972 (Box-folder 8.7)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Research Investigation on Effects of Air Force Propellants on Metabolism Using Radiorespirometry," F 33615-71-C-1516, 1971 (Box-folder 8.8)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Effects of Toxic Agents on Catabolic Mechanisms Using Radiorespirometry," AF 33615-67-C-1787, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 8.9)
  - U.S. Air Force contract: "Effects of Toxic Agents on Catabolic Mechanisms Using Radiorespirometry," AF 33615-67C-1787, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 9.1)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Studies on Environmental Pollution by Missile Propellants," AF 33(615)1767, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 9.2)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Inorganic Fluoride Propellant Oxidizers," AF 33(615)1767, 1968 (Box-folder 9.3)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Studies on Environmental Pollution by Missile Propellants," AF 33(615)-1767, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 9.4)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Studies on Environmental Pollution by Missile Propellants," AF 33(615)-1767, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 9.5)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Studies on Environmental Pollution by Missile Propellants," AF 33(615)-1767, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 9.6)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Metabolism and Pharmacology of Inorganic Fluorine-Containing Compounds," AF 33(615)-1799, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 10.1)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Metabolism and Pharmacology of Inorganic Fluorine-Containing Compounds," AF 33(615)-1799, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 10.2)
  - U.S. Air Force Contract: "Metabolism and Pharmacology of Inorganic Fluorine-Containing Compounds," AF 33(615)-1799, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 10.3)
  - U.S. AEC Contract: "Carbohydrate-Amino Acid Interrelationships Using Isotopic Tracers," AT(45-1)-301, 1952-1960 (Box-folder 10.4)
  - U.S. AEC Contract: "Radiotracer Studies of Intermediary Metabolism in Fruit," AT(45-1)-573, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 10.5)
  - U.S. AEC Contract: "Radiotracer Studies of Intermediary Metabolism in Fruit," AT(45-1)-573, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 10.6)
  - U.S. AEC Contract: "Radiotracers Studies of Biosynthetic and Respiratory Pathways," AT(45-1)-1387, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 11.1)
  - U.S. AEC Contract: "Radiotracers Studies of Biosynthetic and Respiratory Pathways," AT(45-1)-1387, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 11.2)
  - U.S. AEC Contract: "Radiotracers Studies of Biosynthetic and Respiratory Pathways," AT(45-1)-1387, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 11.3)
  - U.S. AEC Contract: "Radiation Chemistry, Photochemistry and Excited States of Oxyanions and DNA," AT(45-1)-2014, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 11.4)
  - U.S. AEC Grants: Nuclear Equipment, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 11.5)
  - U.S. AEC Proposal: "Modal Methods for Computing Fact Spectra", 1966-1969 (Box-folder 11.6)
  - U.S. AEC Proposal: "Reactor Graphite Assistance", 1966 (Box-folder 12.1)
  - U.S. AEC Proposal: "Fluorescence Studies of the Purine and Pyrimidine Bases, Dinucleotides, and DNA at Room Temperature", 1972 (Box-folder 12.2)
  - U.S. AEC Grant Proposal: "Requesting Assistance for Fabrication of Reactor Fuel Elements", 1973 (Box-folder 12.3)
  - U.S. Navy Contract: "Biophysical Models of Radiation Injury", 1970-1972 (Box-folder 12.4)
  - U.S. Navy Contract: "Study to Determine the Effect of Deep Ocean Sediment Constituents on In-Situ Nuclear Water Content Measurement", 1968-1970 (Box-folder 12.5)
  - U.S. Navy Contract: "Medical Neutron Radiography", 1967-1972 (Box-folder 12.6)
  - U.S. Navy Proposal: "The Toxic Action of Certain Rocket Propellants", 1963 (Box-folder 12.7)
  - U.S. Public Health Service Grant: "Comparative Carbohydrate Metabolism of Microorganisms," AI01144, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 12.8)
  - U.S. Public Health Service Grant: "Comparative Carbohydrate Metabolism of Microorganisms," AI01144, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 12.9)
  - U.S. Public Health Service Grant: "Carbohydrate Metabolism in Lymphocytes," AM07223, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 12.10)
  - U.S. Public Health Service Grant: "Effects of Radiation on the Migration of Salmonids," RG-00246-01, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 12.11)
  - U.S. Public Health Service Proposal: "Science Research Institute Building Facilities", 1957 (Box-folder 12.12)
  - Ronald M. Knaus Research Project, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 13.1)
- Training and Education Project Records, 1958-1981; Series III
  This series is composed of materials related to training programs, workshops, and conferences conducted by the OSU Radiation Center and the Institute of Nuclear Science and Engineering between 1962 and 1981. Included are proposals, contracts, reports, budgetary documents, promotional materials, participant evaluations, exams and coursework, course readings, and other administrative documentation, including some content duplicated on film transparencies. Programs represented in this series include the Academic Year Institute in Nuclear Science for College Teachers in Biological Science which offered instruction for biologists undertaking teaching and research in nuclear and radiation sciences; the Summer Workshop on Energy Resources and Electric Power Generation, a program designed to instruct high school educators on the scientific and technical facets of power generation; and a special, annual program to provide technical training in nuclear power generation for employees of TaiPower, Taiwan's state-owned electric power utility. This series also contains records of theses and dissertations overseen by Wang during his tenure at OSU.
  - General Electric Boiling Water Reactor Training Program, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 13.2)
  - NSF Grant: "Development and Implementation of a Four-Year B.S. Curriculum in Nuclear Technology," GT-6180, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 13.3)
  - NSF Summer Institute for College Chemistry Teachers, 1964 (Box-folder 13.4)
  - OSU Workshop: "Liquid Scintillation Counting and Tritium Methodology", 1962 (Box-folder 13.5)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 13.6)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 13.7)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 13.8)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 13.9)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 13.10)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Proposal, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 14.1)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 1 Records, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 14.2)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 2 Records, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 14.3)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 3 Records, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 14.4)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 4 Records, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 14.5)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 5 Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14.6)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 5 Budgetary Records, 1973 (Box-folder 14.7)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 5 Course Materials, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14.8)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 5 Participant Records, 1973 (Box-folder 15.1)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 Memorandum of Understanding, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 15.2)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 15.3)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 P.C. Liu Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 15.4)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 Budgetary Records, 1976 (Box-folder 15.5)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 Activities, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15.6)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 Participant Records, 1975 (Box-folder 15.7)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 Participant Evaluations, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 16.1)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 6 Course Materials, 1975 (Box-folder 16.2)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Program Planning, 1977 (Box-folder 16.3)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16.4)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 P. C. Liu Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 16.5)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Budgetary Records, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16.6)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Activities, 1977 (Box-folder 16.7)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Participant Records, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16.8)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Participant Evaluations, 1977 (Box-folder 17.1)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Course Materials, 1977 (Box-folder 17.2)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 7 Course Materials, 1978 (Box-folder 17.3)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 8 Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.4)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 8 Budgetary Records, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.5)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 8 Activities, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.6)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 8 Participant Records, 1978 (Box-folder 17.7)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 8 Participant Evaluations, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.8)
  - OSU-TaiPower Training Program Group 8 Course Materials, 1978 (Box-folder 17.9)